http://www.firstreliance.com/privacy-policy/

Alerts and Updates
Skip to main content
PRIVACY PRACTICES
Protecting your privacy.
Home
Bottom Menu
Privacy Policy
What does First Reliance Bank do with your personal information?
Why: Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What: The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number
Account Balance and Payment History
Credit History and Credit Scores
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How: All financial companies need to share customers personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reason financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reason First Reliance bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Questions? Call 888-543-5510
Printable Privacy Notice
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does First Reliance share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purpose – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureau
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your transaction and experiences
